<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2014 Richard Hughes <richard@hughsie.com> -->
<!-- HOUSEKEEPING, REMOVE THIS COMMENT WHEN THIS GOES UPSTREAM
BugReportURL: https://sourceforge.net/p/fgrun/support-requests/9/
SentUpstream: 2014-09-17
-->
<component type="desktop">
	<id>org.flightgear.FlightGear</id>
	<name>FlightGear</name>
	<summary>A free and highly sophisticated flight simulator</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="pt_BR">Um simulador de voo gratuito e altamente sofisticado</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="es">Un simulador de vuelo gratuito y altamente sofisticado</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="it">Un simulatore di volo gratuito e altamente sofisticato</summary>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<description>
		<p>FlightGear allows you to control over 400 aircraft, small and large in a range of situations, types of weather, seasons, day and night cycle. This includes single-engine propeller aircraft, large 4-engine passenger liners, experimental aircraft, classic and vintage aircraft and helicopters.</p>
		<p>The FlightGear landscape covers the entire world and is downloaded as you fly. Visit any of the 20,000 airports with an accurate representation of airport buildings on many of the larger, international airports.</p>
		<p>Most popular flight control hardware, such as yokes and sticks are supported. Multiple monitor setup and multiplayer is also featured.</p>
	</description>
	<description xml:lang="pt_BR">
		<p>FlightGear permite controlar mais de 400 aeronaves, pequenas e grandes em diversas situações, tipos de clima, estações do ano, ciclo diurno e noturno. Isso inclui aeronaves a hélice monomotor, grandes navios de passageiros de 4 motores, aeronaves experimentais, aeronaves clássicas e antigas e helicópteros.</p>
		<p>A paisagem do FlightGear cobre o mundo inteiro e é baixada enquanto você voa. Visite qualquer um dos 20.000 aeroportos com uma representação precisa dos edifícios do aeroporto em muitos dos maiores aeroportos internacionais.</p>
		<p>Mais popular hardware de controle de vôo, tais como yokes e sticks são suportados. Vários monitores de configuração e multiplayer também é destaque.</p>
	</description>
	<description xml:lang="es">
		<p>FlightGear permite controlar más de 400 aeronaves, pequeñas y grandes en diversas situaciones, tipos de clima, estaciones del año, ciclo diurno y nocturno. Esto incluye aviones a hélice monomotor, grandes buques de pasajeros de 4 motores, aeronaves experimentales, aeronaves clásicas y antiguas y helicópteros.</p>
		<p>El paisaje de FlightGear cubre el mundo entero y se descarga mientras vuela. Visite cualquiera de los 20.000 aeropuertos con una representación precisa de los edificios del aeropuerto en muchos de los mayores aeropuertos internacionales.</p>
		<p>Más populares hardware de control de vuelo, como yokes y sticks son compatibles. Varios monitores de configuración y multijugador también se destaca.</p>
        </description>
	<description xml:lang="it">
		<p>FlightGear permette di controllare più di 400 velivoli, piccoli e grandi in diverse situazioni, tipo di meteo, stagioni, ciclo diurno e notturno. Questo include velivoli ad elica monomotore, velivoli ad elica monomotore, grandi navi passeggeri a 4 motori, velivoli sperimentali, velivoli ed elicotteri classici e vintage.</p>
		<p>Il paesaggio di FlightGear copre tutto il mondo e viene scaricato mentre voli. Visita uno qualsiasi dei 20.000 aeroporti con una rappresentazione accurata degli edifici aeroportuali su molti dei più grandi aeroporti internazionali.</p>
		<p>Sono supportati i più diffusi hardware di controllo del volo, come gioghi e levette. Sono presenti anche impostazioni per monitor multipli e multiplayer.</p>
	</description>
	<url type="homepage">https://www.flightgear.org/</url>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">
			<image>http://wiki.flightgear.org/images/b/b3/SOTM-Feb18.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>http://wiki.flightgear.org/images/3/37/SOTY-2017.jpeg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>http://wiki.flightgear.org/images/2/27/SOTM-Oct17.png</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>http://wiki.flightgear.org/images/2/22/C172p-preview2.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>http://wiki.flightgear.org/images/7/7f/EC135_Sea_of_fog.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
		<screenshot>
			<image>http://wiki.flightgear.org/images/4/42/Hot_Stuff_with_H130_at_Stromboli.jpg</image>
		</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<content_rating type="oars-1.1">
		<content_attribute id="social-chat">intense</content_attribute>
	</content_rating>
	<project_license>GPL-2.0</project_license>
	<developer_name>FlightGear Developers</developer_name>
	<url type="bugtracker">https://sourceforge.net/p/flightgear/codetickets/</url>
	<url type="donation">https://store.flightgear.org/</url>
	<url type="help">https://flightgear.sourceforge.net/getstart-en/getstart-en.html</url>
	<url type="translate">https://wiki.flightgear.org/Howto:Translate_FlightGear</url>
	<releases>
		<!-- When updating flightgear, add a new line below (don't remove the older ones) and sort them newest-first -->
		<release date="2021-01-24" version="2020.3.6" />
		<release date="2020-12-19" version="2020.3.5" />
		<release date="2020-12-01" version="2020.3.4" />
		<release date="2020-11-23" version="2020.3.3" />
		<release date="2020-05-26" version="2020.1.3" />
		<release date="2019-01-29" version="2018.3.2" />
	</releases>
</component>
